Guide to the Taube Archive of the International Military Tribunal (IMT) at Nuremberg mt839rq8746
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Taube Archive of the International Military Tribunal (IMT) at Nuremberg
1945-46
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
International Military Tribunal
mt839rq8746
398 item(s)
Nuremberg War Crime Trials, Nuremberg, Germany, 1946-1949; Zeppelinfeld (Nuremberg, Germany)
- International Military Tribunal (IMT) at Nuremberg - Document Books, DocBooks; International Military Tribunal
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  International Court of Justice
  Scope and Contents
  The collection in the Virtual Tribunal platform contains approximately 250,000 pages of digitized paper documents (transcripts of the hearings in English, French, German and Russian; written pleadings; evidence exhibits filed by the prosecution and the defense; documents of the Committee for the Investigation and Prosecution of Major War Criminals; the judgment).
  The official archives of the International Military Tribunal of Nuremberg (the "Nuremberg Trial Archives") were entrusted to the International Court of Justice (ICJ) in 1950. The ICJ and its Registry are the custodians of the entire archive, which includes the original print documents that are available in digital form here, audio recordings of the trial's proceedings, and evidentiary films.
  - Martin BORMANN, H-0655; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 1, H-0656; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 2, H-0657; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 3, H-0658; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 4, H-0659; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 1, H-0660; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 2, H-0661; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 3, H-0662; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 4, H-0663; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 5, H-0664; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Wilhelm FRICK, H-0665; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRITZSCHE - No. 1, H-0666; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRITZSCHE - No. 2, H-0667; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hermann GOERING - No. 1, H-0668; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hermann GOERING - No. 2, H-0669; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 1, H-0670; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 2, H-0671; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 3, H-0672; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 1, H-0673; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 2, H-0674; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 3, H-0675; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Ernst KALTENBRUNNER, H-0676; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Wilhelm KEITEL - No. 1, H-0677; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Wilhelm KEITEL - No. 2, H-0678; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 1, H-0679; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 2, H-0680; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 3, H-0681; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 4, H-0682; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 5, H-0683; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 1, H-0684; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 2, H-0685; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 3, H-0686; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 1, H-0687; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Including 7 supplementary loose sheets
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 2, H-0688; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 3, H-0689; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 4, H-0690; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 5, H-0691; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 6, H-0692; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 1 (Vol. 1), H-0693; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 1 (Vol. 2), H-0694; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 2, H-0695; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 3, H-0696; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Martin BORMANN, H-0697; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 1, H-0698; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 2, H-0699; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 3, H-0700; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 4, H-0701; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 1, H-0702; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 2, H-0703; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 3, H-0704; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 4, H-0705; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 5, H-0706; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Wilhelm FRICK, H-0707; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRITZSCHE - No. 1, H-0708; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRITZSCHE - No. 2, H-0709; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hermann GOERING - No. 1, H-0710; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Including a 4-page Supplemental Loose Document
  - Hermann GOERING - No. 2, H-0711; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 1, H-0712; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 2, H-0713; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 3, H-0714; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 1, H-0715; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 2, H-0716; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 3, H-0717; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Ernst KALTENBRUNNER, H-0718; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Wilhelm KEITEL - No. 1, H-0719; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Including a 4-page Loose Document entitled "Grundlagen über die Organization der Deutschen Wehrmacht"
  - Wilhelm KEITEL - No. 2, H-0720; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 1, H-0721; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 2, H-0722; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 3, H-0723; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 4, H-0724; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 5, H-0725; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 1, H-0726; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 2, H-0727; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 3, H-0728; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 1, H-0729; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 2, H-0730; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 108-118 inserted as a Loose Document
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 3, H-0731; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 4, H-0732; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 5, H-0733; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 6, H-0734; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 1 (Vol. 1), H-0735; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 1 (Vol. 2), H-0736; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) p. 153 (a) inserted as a Loose Document
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 2, H-0737; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 3, H-0738; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Martin BORMANN, H-0739; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 1, H-0740; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 2, H-0741; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 3, H-0742; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Karl DOENITZ - No. 4, H-0743; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 1, H-0744; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Including 2 loose sheets
  - Hans FRANK - No. 2, H-0745; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 3, H-0746; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 4, H-0747; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRANK - No. 5, H-0748; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Wilhelm FRICK, H-0749; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRITZSCHE - No. 1, H-0750; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hans FRITZSCHE - No. 2, H-0751; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 26-27 inserted as Loose Document
  - Herman GOERING - No. 1, H-0752; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Herman GOERING - No. 2, H-0753; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 1, H-0754; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 2, H-0755; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Rudolf HESS - No. 3, H-0756; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 1, H-0757; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 2, H-0758; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL - No. 3, H-0759; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Ernst KALTENBRUNNER, H-0760; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Ernst KALTENBRUNNER - Supplement, H-0761; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Wilhelm KEITEL - No. 1, H-0762; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Wilhelm KEITEL - No. 2, H-0763; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 1, H-0764; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 2, H-0765; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 3, H-0766; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 4, H-0767; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Constantin Von NEURATH - No. 5, H-0768; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 1, H-0769; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 2, H-0770; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Franz Von PAPEN - No. 3, H-0771; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 1, H-0772; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 2, H-0773; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 108-118 are inserted as a Loose Document
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 3, H-0774; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 4, H-0775; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 5, H-0776; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Erich RAEDER - No. 6, H-0777; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 1 (Vol. 1), H-0778; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 1 (Vol. 2), H-0779; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 2, H-0780; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred ROSENBERG - No. 3, H-0781; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Walter FUNK, H-0782; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Walter FUNK - supplement, H-0783; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 1, H-0784; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 2, H-0785; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 3, H-0786; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 4, H-0787; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 5, H-0788; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 6, H-0789; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 7, H-0790; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 8, H-0791; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 9, H-0792; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 1, H-0793; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 2, H-0794; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 3, H-0795; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - supplement, H-0796; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 58 pages unbound
  - Hjalmar SCHACHT - No. 1, H-0797; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hjalmar SCHACHT - No. 2, H-0798; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) With 14-page Loose Document identified as "Schacht 48"
  - Baldur von SCHIRACH - No. 1, H-0799; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Baldur von SCHIRACH - No. 2, H-0800; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - No. 1, H-0801; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - No. 2, H-0802; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - supplement, H-0803; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Albert SPEER - No. 1, H-0804; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Albert SPEER - No. 2, H-0805; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Julius STREICHER, H-0806; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Leadership Corps - No. 1 (Political Leaders), H-0807; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Leadership Corps - No. 2 (Political Leaders), H-0808; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Gestapo - No. 1, H-0809; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Gestapo - No. 2, H-0810; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Reich Cabinet, H-0811; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 1, H-0812; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 2, H-0813; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 3, H-0814; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - General Staff - No. 1, H-0815; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - General Staff - No. 2, H-0816; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SA - No. 1 (a), H-0817; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 31 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 1 (b), H-0818; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 29 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 2, H-0819; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 15 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 3, H-0820; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 27 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 4, H-0821; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SA - No. 5, H-0822; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 30 pages, unbound
  - SD, H-0823; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Walter FUNK, H-0824; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Walter FUNK - supplement, H-0825; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 1, H-0826; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 2, H-0827; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 3, H-0828; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 4, H-0829; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 5, H-0830; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 6, H-0831; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 7, H-0832; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 8, H-0833; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 9, H-0834; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 1, H-0835; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 2, H-0836; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 3, H-0837; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - supplement, H-0838; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 58 pages, unbound
  - Hjalmar SCHACHT - No. 1, H-0839; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hjalmar SCHACHT - No. 2, H-0840; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Baldur von SCHIRACH - No. 1, H-0841; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Baldur von SCHIRACH - No. 2, H-0842; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - No. 1, H-0843; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - No. 2, H-0844; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - supplement, H-0845; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Albert SPEER - No. 1, H-0846; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Albert SPEER - No. 2, H-0847; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Julius STREICHER, H-0848; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Leadership Corps - No. 1 (Political Leaders), H-0849; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Leadership Corps - No. 2 (Political Leaders), H-0850; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Gestapo - No. 1, H-0851; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Gestapo - No. 2, H-0852; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Reich cabinet, H-0853; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 1, H-0854; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 2, H-0855; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 3, H-0856; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - General Staff - No. 1, H-0857; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - General Staff - No. 2, H-0858; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SA - No. 1 (a), H-0859; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 30 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 1 (b), H-0860; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 28 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 2, H-0861; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 14 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 3, H-0862; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 27 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 4, H-0863; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SA - No. 5, H-0864; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 22 pages, unbound. Note: Defense Document Book SD, German, is missing
  - Walter FUNK, H-0865; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Walter FUNK (Supplement, May 3), 1946-05-03; H-0866; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Walter FUNK (Supplement, May 10), 1946-05-10; H-0867; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 1, H-0868; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 2, H-0869; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 3, H-0870; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 4, H-0871; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 5, H-0872; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 6, H-0873; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 7, H-0874; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 8, H-0875; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Joachim von RIBBENTROP - No. 9, H-0876; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 1, H-0877; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 2, H-0878; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Fritz SAUCKEL - No. 3, H-0879; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Note: Defense Document Book - SAUCKEL - Supplement, is missing in French
  - Hjalmar SCHACHT - No. 1, H-0880; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Hjalmar SCHACHT - No. 2, H-0881; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Baldur von SCHIRACH - No. 1, H-0882; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Baldur von SCHIRACH - No. 2, H-0883; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - No. 1, H-0884; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - No. 2, H-0885; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Arthur SEYSS-INQUART - supplement, H-0886; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Albert SPEER - No. 1, H-0887; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Albert SPEER - No. 2, H-0888; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Julius STREICHER, H-0889; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Leadership Corps (Political Leaders) No. 1, H-0890; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Leadership Corps (Political Leaders) - No. 2, H-0891; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Gestapo - No. 1, H-0892; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Gestapo - No. 2, H-0893; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Reich Cabinet, H-0894; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 1, H-0895; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 2, H-0896; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SS - No. 3, H-0897; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - General Staff - No. 1, H-0898; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - General Staff - No. 2, H-0899; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SA - No. 1 (a), H-0900; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 36 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 1 (b), H-0901; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 35 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 2, H-0902; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 21 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 3, H-0903; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 32 pages, unbound
  - SA - No. 4, H-0904; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SA - No. 5, H-0905; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 32 pages, unbound
  - SD, H-0906; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book A: Common Objectives, Methods and Doctrines of the Conspiracy., H-1096; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book B: The acquiring of Totalitarian Control over Germany: Political; First Steps; Control acquired., H-1098; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book C: Consolidation of Control; Utilization and molding of Political Machinery., H-1100; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book D: Reshaping of Education; Training of Youth, H-1102; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book E: Propaganda, Censorship and Supervision of Cultural Activities, H-1104; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book F: Purge of Political Opponents; Terrorization, H-1106; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book G: Destruction of the Free Trade Unions and the Acquisition of Control over the Productive Labor capacity of Germany, H-1108; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book H: Suppression of the Christian Churches in Germany, H-1110; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book H, Supplemental: Suppression of the Christian Churches in Germany and in the Occupied Territories, H-1112; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book I: Adoption and Publication of the Program for Persecution of the Jews, H-1114; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book J: Militarization of Nazi Dominated Organizations, H-1116; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book K: Economic aspects of the Conspiracy, H-1118; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)